<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Posts on Bob Florian</title>
		<link>https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/</link>
		<description>Recent content in Posts on Bob Florian</description>
		<generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
		<language>en-us</language>
		<copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 00:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate>
		<atom:link href="https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
		<item>
			<title>Thailand - Day 11 - Tuesday</title>
			<link>https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/thailand/day-11-tuesday-31/</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
			
			<guid>https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/thailand/day-11-tuesday-31/</guid>
			<description>We wake up at the hill tribe lodge and meet Waza for breakfast, at you guessed it, a buffet breakfast.
Today we drive to back to Chiang Mai, but first stop is at the ELEPHANTS. We go to the Elephant Nature Park near Chiang Mai, which is a sanctuary for Elephants. Many of the local tourist places that tout riding them are very bad to visit. The owner of the ENP tells us his story, the story of each elephant, and why he treats them all differently here.</description>
			<content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We wake up at the hill tribe lodge and meet Waza for breakfast, at you guessed it, a buffet breakfast.</p>

<p>Today we drive to back to Chiang Mai, but first stop is at the ELEPHANTS.  We go to the Elephant Nature Park near Chiang Mai, which is a sanctuary for Elephants.  Many of the local tourist places that tout riding them are very bad to visit.  The owner of the ENP tells us his story, the story of each elephant, and why he treats them all differently here.</p>

<p>We need to dress in some local garb, and so that the elephants kind of recognize us as someone who wants to help with them and feed them.</p>

<p>They eat so much food!  After hearing all of the historical information we finally get to go meet the elephants.  There are 6 of them today to be with us.  They are ready and lined up for snacks!  Today we all feed them snacks of bananas and sugar cane.  They are very gentle with their trunks.  They can very easily take a banana from your hands.  Sometimes they&rsquo;ll hold on to 20-30 bananas and sugar cane before stuffing it into their mouths!  We all took turns and fed them many times for about 20 minutes.</p>

<p>From here we walked through the landscape and hills and stopped every once and a while to learn some more about the care of them and what it takes.  They try to grow as much of the food on site, but they cannot grow enough to meet their needs, so they buy <em>organic only</em> food from local suppliers.</p>

<p>Sometimes the elephants stop and scratch on a tree of stick, which is kind of funny to watch.  They are so good with their trunks that they can pick up a stick off the ground to scratch their backs or bellies with.</p>

<p>The owner carries a large knife, and he kindly explains why since some people might be aprehensive.  He said it&rsquo;s not ever for use against elephants or people.  Mostly to cut food, plants in the way, and for snakes!  Cobras can be particularly vicious as he explains, but he&rsquo;s not afraid of them anymore.</p>

<p>Back to RatiLanna, for new years party!  it&rsquo;s much more crowded at the hotel now.</p>
]]></content>
		</item>
		
		<item>
			<title>Thailand - Day 09 - Sunday</title>
			<link>https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/thailand/day-09-sunday-29/</link>
			<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
			
			<guid>https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/thailand/day-09-sunday-29/</guid>
			<description>From Chiang Mai we ventured toward the mountain village of Mae Kampong, which is a hilly resort village of sorts where many many locals come to get away from the busy cities.
On the way we stopped at a temple in Chiang Mai, Wat Suan Dok, where we learned much history, toured the grounds, and waited for our time to have a Monk Chat. While waiting for our time to listen, and talk with a local monk, we visited the enjoyed the main grounds of the temple.</description>
			<content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>From Chiang Mai we ventured toward the mountain village of Mae Kampong, which is a hilly resort village of sorts where many many locals come to get away from the busy cities.</p>

<p>On the way we stopped at a temple in Chiang Mai, Wat Suan Dok, where we learned much history, toured the grounds, and waited for our time to have a Monk Chat.  While waiting for our time to listen, and talk with a local monk, we visited the enjoyed the main grounds of the temple.  We partook in the custom of dropping coins in the 108 bowls, representing the 108 concerns of the Buddha.</p>

<p>Our time came to visit with a local monk, and we joined with a couple other small groups of tourists.  One other family of 5 happened to be from Chicago!  They were from Wrigleyville, and doing a similar trip as to us.  The other two guys were from Canada.  For the next 1.5 hours the monk gave us history, knowledge, and philosophy of Buddhism, which was very enlightening.  The other groups had many questions about the philosophy, history, practices, rules, etiquette, and daily lives of the monks.  It&rsquo;s a very different perspective on life that is very intriguing.</p>

<p>The journey continues on to MaeKampong.</p>

<p>We met our host family, and found where we were staying for the night.  The accommodations were very simple.  Our &ldquo;room&rdquo;, was a separate building on the side of the hill, kind of attached to the rest of the family&rsquo;s set of buildings.  It was right above the kitchen.  Our room was about 20x20, but with just two queen mattresses on the floor and a bunch of blankets.  It was noticeably cooler here, and at night it would be cold.  Good thing we brought our jackets.  The bathroom was outside, and was a combo shower/toilet in one.  Very simple accommodations, but ample.</p>

<p>We rested up for a bit and then went for a hike with the middle aged women of the family.  I&rsquo;m pretty sure there were 4 generations of family living in this homestead. We hiked through town, and then into the woods where a nice stream was running down the mountain.  The guide showed us tea trees they harvest for tea, among other things.  Sprinkled through the woods were some coffee bushes/trees too.  Our goal was the top of the mountain, where there was a coffee shop.  Once there I got a iced Thai tea, and Chrissy got an iced coffee.  Can&rsquo;t remember what Aiden got.  But the view from up here was amazing.  It would be wonderful to wake up to something like this every day.</p>

<p>At one point we had stopped where the local family roasts coffee, and they showed us the sorting, roasting process.  It smelled SO GOOD in this small building.</p>

<p>We hiked back down and took some time to rest before dinner.  The eldest woman was going to cook dinner for us and invited us to come down and help cook.  So about 530 we came down to help where we were tasked with chopping vegetables. She had already made the green curry for the port dish, and Aiden and I made the stir fry vegetables with an egg in it.  There was also rice and a couple other things too, everything was very good!  Aiden invited our driver to eat with us, and he also brought some fermented bamboo shoots from home since he was near home (he lived in Chiang Mai)</p>

<p>After dinner we just watched the rain from the balcony we had on our level of the hill complex and played Uno! which we had acquired in a market a couple days before.  Then bed.</p>
]]></content>
		</item>
		
		<item>
			<title>Thailand - Day 06 - Thursday</title>
			<link>https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/thailand/day-06-thursday-dec-26/</link>
			<pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
			
			<guid>https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/thailand/day-06-thursday-dec-26/</guid>
			<description>Today is a travel day; 7+ hours in the van from Kanachaburi to Sukhothai. We ate breakfast at the camp hotel one more time and then checked out of the first hotel.
We traveled very far for many km during the day. We stopped at many gas stations and rest stops for breaks, snacks, and to stretch our legs.
Waza bought us some strange nuts, that looked like water buffalo head, which were very hard to open, but tasty inside.</description>
			<content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Today is a travel day; 7+ hours in the van from Kanachaburi to Sukhothai. We ate breakfast at the camp hotel one more time and then checked out of the first hotel.</p>

<p>We traveled very far for many km during the day. We stopped at many gas stations and rest stops for breaks, snacks, and to stretch our legs.</p>

<p>Waza bought us some strange nuts, that looked like water buffalo head, which were very hard to open, but tasty inside.</p>

<p>She also bought so many other snacks we cannot eat anymore. I have declared I&rsquo;m full for the next few days.</p>

<p>Every once and a while we will just stop for fun at a roadside market and see the local warez, food, and chat with the local people. No one speaks English, so Waza translates for us.</p>

<p>For lunch we stopped at a local town Sam Chuey ?? (sp) and walked the local market first. This was a very typical local market with everything you could think of. Waza gave us samples of what she thought was safe to eat, and yummy. We ate Pork meat balls, some kind of jelly fruit balls, banana chips, fried bananas with sesame.</p>

<p>Then it was time for lunch, when we were already full!  We didn&rsquo;t really want to eat at all, but Waza took us into a restaurant that seemed more upscale for the food market, since it had AC. We ate several kinds of noodle soups. Wide flat noodles with pork and veggies. Small flat yellow noodles with pork meat&hellip;. and pork blood&hellip; which we didn&rsquo;t eat, but I recognized it from some other food videos I&rsquo;ve watched.</p>

<p>After lunch we walked the market some more, and then found the Van, for which we took a nap after lunch.</p>

<p>During the drive there was some traffic, and people sell snacks to people sitting in traffic. So of course Waza bought some &ldquo;traffic donuts&rdquo; which were very very good; almost like Krispy Kremes. But the extra food did not sit well. Becoming aware of how much food we have been eating in an uncomfortable way.</p>

<p>After a bit more driving we have arrived at our new hotel, in Sukhothai, Thailand. We are staying at Legendha Resort, which is next to some of the old ancient templates. The pool is very nice and Aiden went swimming, while Chrissy and I got some drinks near the bar, after smothering ourselves in mosquito spray, as they are very strong here. Aiden counted the lizards on the walls, maybe 15+ at one time.</p>

<p>After swimming we got ready for DINNER. MORE FOOD. CANNOT TAKE IT ANYMORE. They brought out no less than 5 dishes, rice, and soup. I literally took one bite of each thing, and felt so bad because it was very very good food. Tomorrow I&rsquo;m not eating anything.</p>

<p>There was an interpretive dance during dinner which was neat, but Aiden was falling asleep during dinner, so we left, and said goodnight to Waza ,and will meet her for BREAKFAST in the morning. Which I will likely not eat, since I&rsquo;m so full.</p>
]]></content>
		</item>
		
		<item>
			<title>Thailand - Day 05 - Wednesday</title>
			<link>https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/thailand/day-05-wednesday-dec-25/</link>
			<pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
			
			<guid>https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/thailand/day-05-wednesday-dec-25/</guid>
			<description>Day two, and night two at the Hintok River Camp at Hellfire Pass We woke up about 600 to the sounds of roosters in the neighborhood!
Got dressed and packed for the day of adventure
Met our guide, Waza, for breakfast. Was mostly traditional western style breakfast but I chose the Thai dishes of pork rice porridge soup which I added cilantro, basil, picked peppers, and pepper flakes. Super yummy, and not something I would have considered for breakfast.</description>
			<content type="html"><![CDATA[

<h1 id="day-two-and-night-two-at-the-hintok-river-camp-at-hellfire-pass">Day two, and night two at the Hintok River Camp at Hellfire Pass</h1>

<p>We woke up about 600 to the sounds of roosters in the neighborhood!</p>

<p>Got dressed and packed for the day of adventure</p>

<p>Met our guide, Waza, for breakfast. Was mostly traditional western style breakfast but I chose the Thai dishes of pork rice porridge soup which I added cilantro, basil, picked peppers, and pepper flakes.  Super yummy, and not something I would have considered for breakfast.</p>

<p>After breakfast we hopped in the van for a 1 hour ride to the &ldquo;camp&rdquo; where we were to ride bikes and kayak. The camp was a very large facility where locals come, school groups and such. there was an olympic size pool even.</p>

<p>We were met by our local guide for this trip, and the person to give the safety briefing. Safety guy was seemingly a French national, and his English was very good and refined. He gave us a 5 minute safety briefing about paddling, and then about the bikes and how to change gears and brake (which wasn&rsquo;t really needed in our case)</p>

<p>After the safety briefing we were off with our guide PiaPia into the countryside of the area, where we rode through the local farms, countryside, and along some main roads with all of the crazy drivers and motor bikes. We saw banana trees, jackfruit, rubber trees, long beans, basil and other unidentifiable things. They were surprised that I had Thai basil growing at home, but I explained that many Americans grow herb gardens in their kitchens. After biking a few km we stopped at a local farmers work station where they were processing long beans. Our guide just hopped off his bike, told Aiden to &ldquo;come here&rdquo; - &ldquo;try a bean&rdquo; and pulled a bean off the vine and we all ate some; which was kind of like a mix between a string bean and edamame, but a little sweeter. After biking a little bit further, we stopped at a local fruit stand in the middle of no where. There were 3 people, seemingly 3 generations of ladies working the farm stand and one gentlemen cleaning and processing jack fruit. Our guide bought some jack fruit off them for us for a snack, and it was very very good. Kind of like a crunchy melon!  We&rsquo;ll have to see if we can find any in the US when we get back. Here we also tried some pickled tamarind, which was just OK, but the locals gave us some powder to put on the tamarind, which was sour-something; and kind of made the tamarind into a sour candy type of thing; it was pretty good, but the jack fruit was better. After just a few more km; the biking portion was over, and on to the kayaking.</p>

<p>Oh, I forgot, during the entire bike ride, we had a truck following us with our kayaks. Whenever we had to cross the street, the guy in the truck would get out and stop traffic for us by standing in it!</p>

<p>For the kayaking we switched into our water shoes and got right into the paddling. There were many floating houses on the river, some more or less shanty&rsquo;s, but some were near luxurious.   We paddled and paddled for about an hour, seeing the villages and river&rsquo;s inner workings.</p>

<p>After paddling we finished up, and cleaned up for a short trip back in the van. Aiden tried the climbing wall just a bit, and the guide helped him without a harness. For lunch we stopped at a seemingly very nice restaurant, where we had cachew chicken, vegetables, and our guide shared some local spicy soup, which was very spicy, but very tasty. It had all sorts of chicken bits, bones and unidentifiable pieces in it. Waza bought us all some ice cream for desert, which was very good chocolate ice cream cones.</p>

<p>After finishing lunch we needed to drive to the Erawan National Park, where there are many many tiered waterfalls. We hiked up to &ldquo;level 4&rdquo; - which is all we had time before since the Rangers/Soldiers started to close levels off beginning at 330pm. The water was pretty cold, but I put my feet in, and Aiden went all in most places. There were many many lamprey fish &ldquo;doctor fish&rdquo;, who will eat the dead skin off your leg and feet. If you keep still they will come up and just start pecking at you, which was very very strange. We stayed at station 3 for about 20 minutes while Aiden swam with all of the other tourists. Then we hiked up 4, then 2, and back to one. Aiden swam at all of them. He tried to catch a fish, but it was very very hard. At the one station there were rock slides, where Aiden went down many many times, and lost his water shoe!  Some local Thai boys tried to find it for him, but could not, as it was too deep.</p>

<p>After the park, we stopped to get some iced coffee, where it seems that coffee is stronger, and better here&hellip; not suer why, will need to find out.</p>

<p>For our drive back our guide stopped off at another hotel resort she was friendly with, and they let us swim in the hot tub and pool; where we met some people from Nevada, and talked with another guide, who was leading 15 Germans though the country. The hot tub was very hot, and pool was cold, but it was very nice. There was a place where Aiden could feed some fish, and did so several times with some other local kids.</p>

<p>After this it was a short ride back to the camp where our driver got lost several times since it was very very dark out.  (Event with using Google Maps!)</p>

<p>We got dinner straight away, Aiden tried to roast some marshmallows that we picked up at a 7-11, but the bamboo fire was too too hot. One glass of wine later and it was time for bed. Wake up call is at 6am to pack, breakfast, and be on the road by 8am for an all day drive to Sukhothai - the ancient land of Thailand, and prior capital. Waza said she&rsquo;ll be stopping at many places for us to stretch, eat, and see some local markets.</p>

<p>Oh, by the way, it&rsquo;s Christmas!  It&rsquo;s hard to tell here, since the days have started to run together, and no locals here celebrate it, but that&rsquo;s OK!</p>
]]></content>
		</item>
		
		<item>
			<title>Thailand - Day 03 - Monday</title>
			<link>https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/thailand/day-03-monday-dec-23/</link>
			<pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
			
			<guid>https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/thailand/day-03-monday-dec-23/</guid>
			<description>Woke up after sleeping for 13-14 hours!
Got room service of Chinese Breakfast, scrambled eggs, bacon, and pork belly bbq breakfast for Aiden. Multiple coffees!
Private Bangkok tour with our guide Eddie! At 1030am we had to meet our local guide Eddie for a tour of Bangkok. I booked Eddie through TripAdvisor. He was waiting for us in the hotel lobby at the arranged time. We quickly discussed a plan of what to do and embarked on our trip.</description>
			<content type="html"><![CDATA[

<p>Woke up after sleeping for 13-14 hours!</p>

<p>Got room service of Chinese Breakfast, scrambled eggs, bacon, and pork belly bbq breakfast for Aiden. Multiple coffees!</p>

<h4 id="private-bangkok-tour-with-our-guide-eddie">Private Bangkok tour with our guide Eddie!</h4>

<p>At 1030am we had to meet our local guide Eddie for a tour of Bangkok. I booked Eddie through <a href="https://www.tripadvisor.com/AttractionProductReview-g293916-d11456468-Private_Guide_In_and_Around_Bangkok_Custom_Tour-Bangkok.html">TripAdvisor</a>. He was waiting for us in the hotel lobby at the arranged time. We quickly discussed a plan of what to do and embarked on our trip. We left for the SkyTrain which was pretty neat. It was kind of like the EL in Chicago, but nicely air conditioned. He explained that most locals cannot afford to ride the train as it&rsquo;s kind of expensive.</p>

<p>After a short ride on the SkyTrain, we got on a ferry boat to ride up the river a bit to the farthest place.</p>

<p>First stop was the Grand Palace, where there were countless Template and buildings. Everything is very picturesque. We walked around here for about an hour taking pictures and seeing things.  It was very very crowded, even on a weekday.</p>

<h4 id="wat-pho-the-reclining-buddha">Wat Pho - the reclining Buddha</h4>

<h4 id="wat-arun-temple-of-the-dawn">Wat Arun - Temple of the Dawn</h4>

<p>We ended at the biggest flower market in Bangkok, which was insane!  So many flowers, smells, and people!  Aiden was just walking around in front of us and didn&rsquo;t see a motor bike <em>inside the market</em> and our guide had to grab him out of the way!</p>

<p>After this we were really tired of walking around and seeing things so we said goodbye to our guide, where he called us a Grab back to our hotel.</p>

<p>For dinner we went to the sushi restaurant in the hotel lobby, <a href="https://guide.michelin.com/en/bangkok-region/bangkok/restaurant/zuma#">Zuma</a>, which was pretty good, including the deserts!</p>

<p>[pics of food here]</p>
]]></content>
		</item>
		
		<item>
			<title>Thailand - Day 02 - Sunday</title>
			<link>https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/thailand/day-02-saturday-21-sunday-22/</link>
			<pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
			
			<guid>https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/thailand/day-02-saturday-21-sunday-22/</guid>
			<description>Woke up at the airport, kind of, since sleeping here is hard&amp;hellip; and indeed we&amp;rsquo;ve lost a day due to huge time difference and travel! The days are beginnging to blur together already. There are mens only, womens only, and family quiet rooms; but we didn&amp;rsquo;t try any of these this time. They didn&amp;rsquo;t seem that comfortable or relaxing.
2am local time, flight from Doha, Qatar to Bangkok, Thailand. Due to late seating selections I had to sit next to someone else, a young French girl traveling alone, who had no concept of personal space.</description>
			<content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Woke up at the airport, kind of, since sleeping here is hard&hellip; and indeed we&rsquo;ve lost a day due to huge time difference and travel!  The days are beginnging to blur together already. There are mens only, womens only, and family quiet rooms; but we didn&rsquo;t try any of these this time. They didn&rsquo;t seem that comfortable or relaxing.</p>

<p>2am local time, flight from Doha, Qatar to Bangkok, Thailand. Due to late seating selections I had to sit next to someone else, a young French girl traveling alone, who had no concept of personal space. She kept elbowing me and putting her feet on my side!  Good thing it was a relatively short flight.</p>

<p>Supposed to arrive at the airport, find our driver, and travel to the hotel.</p>

<p>The Bangkok airport is a <em>HOT MESS</em>. So many people everywhere without regard for personal space. Immigration is awful. The line was several thousand people long, and queuing is about what I expected with people just walking up to the front of the line. At some point the Royal Police decided the line was getting too out of hand they started letting people go into the expedited priority lines that are usually for Thai Nationals. We got selected &ldquo;one time only, special pass for you!&rdquo; by one of the officers. Still felt like a mistake as the Officer processing things was NOT in a hurry, and still took 30 minutes to process about 20 people. Once through our bags were just on the floor instead of on the carousel.</p>

<p>Next, we had to try and find our driver, and wow. After customs the airport was just a mass of people. I forgot to print out our directions on where to meet the driver, but we saw a large group of drivers holding signs with names, so we stood there for 30 minutes waiting for our name on a sign. Started to get really frustrated as they were supposed to be there, so I took a walk down the long (<sup>1</sup>&frasl;<sub>4</sub> mile) terminal and subsequently found 8 more stops with drivers standing around!  The last one I went to I finally found our name, so I had to trek alllll the way back to the beginning where Chrissy and Aiden are waiting to yet again carry our bags all the way through the throngs of people who have no regard for walking and personal space, especially with the hand carts too; I think I got hit twice by them.</p>

<p>Once we told the person with our sign that we were here, she said &ldquo;oh, you are here! So sorry, but your driver left. He only waited for 2 hours&rdquo;. I argued with her that why would the 2 hours start immediately when our plane landed?  It takes time to come through immigration and find your bags. It took probably 2 hours just for us to get through the immigration   She was still adamant that the car was gone; and I would need to go find my own taxi or car somewhere else and pay for it again!  I said no, you find me a car since you stranded me. I was supposed to have Black car service to our hotel, but I&rdquo;m pretty sure she just called me an Uber like service (Grab) b/c she and her &lsquo;manager&rdquo; felt bad. Luckily the car came in about 10 minutes and gave us the 40 minute ride to the hotel in downtown Bangkok.</p>

<p>Arriving at the hotel was welcomed, since traffic got a little crazy toward the ends with all of the motor bikes weaving in and out of cars with no regard for safety. The porters and reception immediately took all bags out of the car and took us up to the reception office on the 12th floor of the hotel. They offered Thai iced tea to all of us, and cookies for Aiden, but he was so out of sorts he didn&rsquo;t want anything!  He just needed to really sleep.</p>

<p>After getting to our room we waited for the butler to bring our bags and then really needed to shower the 30 hours of travel off of us.</p>

<p>I planned on wandering around the neighborhood since it looked very active and vibrant with restaurants, shopping, and several malls but after showers we laid down to rest and then fell asleep for 13 hours, skipping dinner!</p>

<p>The view from our hotel is pretty nice though :)</p>

<p>[pic here]</p>

<p>picture of welcome foods from the hotel!</p>
]]></content>
		</item>
		
		<item>
			<title>Thailand - Day 01 - Friday</title>
			<link>https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/thailand/day-01-friday-dec-20/</link>
			<pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
			
			<guid>https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/thailand/day-01-friday-dec-20/</guid>
			<description>Bolingbrook - 2pm local time. All packed and ready to go! We&amp;rsquo;ve minimized what we&amp;rsquo;re bringing with to just a small duffle bag and a backpack each. (for 2 weeks!)
Car service was supposed to pick us up at 2pm, but he was 15 minutes late. You&amp;rsquo;d think they try to be early or on-time as they know we&amp;rsquo;re going to the airport. No one needs this kind of stress before an international flight.</description>
			<content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Bolingbrook - 2pm local time. All packed and ready to go!  We&rsquo;ve minimized what we&rsquo;re bringing with to just a small duffle bag and a backpack each. (for 2 weeks!)</p>

<p>Car service was supposed to pick us up at 2pm, but he was 15 minutes late. You&rsquo;d think they try to be early or on-time as they know we&rsquo;re going to the airport. No one needs this kind of stress before an international flight.</p>

<p>630pm Flight to Doha, Qatar</p>

<p>9 hour layover in Doha, plan is to likely stay in the airport and some sleeping.</p>

<p>Ate at an Italian place for dinner, greek salad and pizzas. My Greek salad wasn&rsquo;t so great, oh well.</p>

<p>Wandered the airport multiple times, there were several mini parks for kids to play on. Aiden had fun climbing on the structures in the parks.</p>

<p>The airport is very nice, modern, and easy to navigate &ndash; with all signs in English and Arabic. Ended up doing about 18000 steps in the airport to keep busy.</p>
]]></content>
		</item>
		
		<item>
			<title>My First Post - Image Testing</title>
			<link>https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/image-testing/</link>
			<pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 12:39:17 -0600</pubDate>
			
			<guid>https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/image-testing/</guid>
			<description>       $(&#39;#lightgallery&#39;).lightGallery({ thumbnail:true });  </description>
			<content type="html"><![CDATA[<div id="lightgallery">
    <a href="/img/day1/1.jpg">
        <img src="/img/day1/1.jpg" />
    </a> 
        <a href="/img/day1/2.jpg">
        <img src="/img/day1/2.jpg" />
    </a>
        <a href="/img/day1/3.jpg">
        <img src="/img/day1/3.jpg" />
    </a>
        <a href="/img/day1/4.jpg">
        <img src="/img/day1/4.jpg" />
    </a>
        <a href="/img/day1/5.jpg">
        <img src="/img/day1/5.jpg" />
    </a>
        <a href="/img/day1/6.jpg">
        <img src="/img/day1/6.jpg" />
    </a> 
</div>

<script type="text/javascript">
$('#lightgallery').lightGallery({
    thumbnail:true
}); 
</script>
]]></content>
		</item>
		
		<item>
			<title>My First Post - Using Hugo Static Site Generator</title>
			<link>https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/my-first-post/</link>
			<pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 12:39:17 -0600</pubDate>
			
			<guid>https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
			<description>This is my site, there are many like it, but this one is mine.
This site is built from the following tech:
 Code stored in GitHub
 All it takes to publish a new post, or correct something is a push to this repository. AWS Amplify takes care of everything else, like hosting, CDN, deployments. I can even post things from my cell phone if I wanted (because I set up some dev tools to author MarkDown pages and push to GitHub)   Hugo Static site generator</description>
			<content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><em>This is my site, there are many like it, but this one is mine.</em></p>

<p>This site is built from the following tech:</p>

<ul>
<li><p>Code stored in <a href="https://www.github.com">GitHub</a></p>

<ul>
<li>All it takes to publish a new post, or correct something is a push to this repository. AWS Amplify takes care of everything else, like hosting, CDN, deployments. I can even post things from my cell phone if I wanted (because I set up some dev tools to author MarkDown pages and push to GitHub)
<br /></li>
</ul></li>

<li><p><a href="https://gohugo.io/">Hugo</a> Static site generator</p></li>

<li><p>Theme by <a href="https://themes.gohugo.io/hermit/">Hermit</a></p></li>

<li><p><a href="https://usefathom.com/">Fathom Analytics</a></p></li>

<li><p><a href="https://disqus.com/">Disqus</a> commenting</p></li>

<li><p><a href="https://aws.amazon.com/amplify/">AWS Amplify</a> hosting</p></li>

<li><p><a href="https://aws.amazon.com/route53/">AWS Route53</a> for DNS</p></li>
</ul>
]]></content>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
