<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bob Florian</title>
    <link>https://www.bobflorian.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Bob Florian</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 00:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.bobflorian.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Thailand - Day 11 - Tuesday</title>
      <link>https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/thailand/day-11-tuesday-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/thailand/day-11-tuesday-31/</guid>
      <description>We wake up at the hill tribe lodge and meet Waza for breakfast, at you guessed it, a buffet breakfast.
Today we drive to back to Chiang Mai, but first stop is at the ELEPHANTS. We go to the Elephant Nature Park near Chiang Mai, which is a sanctuary for Elephants. Many of the local tourist places that tout riding them are very bad to visit. The owner of the ENP tells us his story, the story of each elephant, and why he treats them all differently here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thailand - Day 09 - Sunday</title>
      <link>https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/thailand/day-09-sunday-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/thailand/day-09-sunday-29/</guid>
      <description>From Chiang Mai we ventured toward the mountain village of Mae Kampong, which is a hilly resort village of sorts where many many locals come to get away from the busy cities.
On the way we stopped at a temple in Chiang Mai, Wat Suan Dok, where we learned much history, toured the grounds, and waited for our time to have a Monk Chat. While waiting for our time to listen, and talk with a local monk, we visited the enjoyed the main grounds of the temple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thailand - Day 06 - Thursday</title>
      <link>https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/thailand/day-06-thursday-dec-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/thailand/day-06-thursday-dec-26/</guid>
      <description>Today is a travel day; 7+ hours in the van from Kanachaburi to Sukhothai. We ate breakfast at the camp hotel one more time and then checked out of the first hotel.
We traveled very far for many km during the day. We stopped at many gas stations and rest stops for breaks, snacks, and to stretch our legs.
Waza bought us some strange nuts, that looked like water buffalo head, which were very hard to open, but tasty inside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thailand - Day 05 - Wednesday</title>
      <link>https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/thailand/day-05-wednesday-dec-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/thailand/day-05-wednesday-dec-25/</guid>
      <description>Day two, and night two at the Hintok River Camp at Hellfire Pass We woke up about 600 to the sounds of roosters in the neighborhood!
Got dressed and packed for the day of adventure
Met our guide, Waza, for breakfast. Was mostly traditional western style breakfast but I chose the Thai dishes of pork rice porridge soup which I added cilantro, basil, picked peppers, and pepper flakes. Super yummy, and not something I would have considered for breakfast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thailand - Day 03 - Monday</title>
      <link>https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/thailand/day-03-monday-dec-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/thailand/day-03-monday-dec-23/</guid>
      <description>Woke up after sleeping for 13-14 hours!
Got room service of Chinese Breakfast, scrambled eggs, bacon, and pork belly bbq breakfast for Aiden. Multiple coffees!
Private Bangkok tour with our guide Eddie! At 1030am we had to meet our local guide Eddie for a tour of Bangkok. I booked Eddie through TripAdvisor. He was waiting for us in the hotel lobby at the arranged time. We quickly discussed a plan of what to do and embarked on our trip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thailand - Day 02 - Sunday</title>
      <link>https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/thailand/day-02-saturday-21-sunday-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/thailand/day-02-saturday-21-sunday-22/</guid>
      <description>Woke up at the airport, kind of, since sleeping here is hard&amp;hellip; and indeed we&amp;rsquo;ve lost a day due to huge time difference and travel! The days are beginnging to blur together already. There are mens only, womens only, and family quiet rooms; but we didn&amp;rsquo;t try any of these this time. They didn&amp;rsquo;t seem that comfortable or relaxing.
2am local time, flight from Doha, Qatar to Bangkok, Thailand. Due to late seating selections I had to sit next to someone else, a young French girl traveling alone, who had no concept of personal space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thailand - Day 01 - Friday</title>
      <link>https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/thailand/day-01-friday-dec-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/thailand/day-01-friday-dec-20/</guid>
      <description>Bolingbrook - 2pm local time. All packed and ready to go! We&amp;rsquo;ve minimized what we&amp;rsquo;re bringing with to just a small duffle bag and a backpack each. (for 2 weeks!)
Car service was supposed to pick us up at 2pm, but he was 15 minutes late. You&amp;rsquo;d think they try to be early or on-time as they know we&amp;rsquo;re going to the airport. No one needs this kind of stress before an international flight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post - Image Testing</title>
      <link>https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/image-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 12:39:17 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/image-testing/</guid>
      <description>       $(&#39;#lightgallery&#39;).lightGallery({ thumbnail:true });  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post - Using Hugo Static Site Generator</title>
      <link>https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 12:39:17 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.bobflorian.com/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>This is my site, there are many like it, but this one is mine.
This site is built from the following tech:
 Code stored in GitHub
 All it takes to publish a new post, or correct something is a push to this repository. AWS Amplify takes care of everything else, like hosting, CDN, deployments. I can even post things from my cell phone if I wanted (because I set up some dev tools to author MarkDown pages and push to GitHub)   Hugo Static site generator</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>